Jensen won CEO of NVIDIA, fresh off his
keynote last night on stage.
Jensen 刚刚卸任 NVIDIA 首席执行官
昨晚在舞台上发表主题演讲。
Great to see you.
Welcome to Las Vegas.
很高兴见到你。
欢迎来到拉斯维加斯。
Happy New Year.
Familiar territory.
新年快乐。
熟悉的领域。
Congratulations on your new baby.
Thank you very much.
恭喜您有了新宝宝。
非常感谢。
A lot's changed since we last spoke,
actually.
自我们上次交谈以来，发生了很多变化，
实际上。
But it's the broad spectrum of what you
announced last night.
但它是您所了解的广泛范围
昨晚宣布。
New graphics cards, new chips, actually,
technically in the automotive space,
新显卡，新芯片，实际上，
从技术上讲，在汽车领域，
products and services on the software
side.
软件上的产品和服务
Which is the single most important for
Nvidia's future.
哪一个对于
Nvidia 的未来。
They're all important.
You know, it's hard.
它们都很重要。
你知道，这很难。
It's single.
It's hard.
它是单身。
这很难。
It's hard.
It's hard to pick your favorites.
这很难。
很难选出您最喜欢的。
You know, we announced three chips.
We announced a brand new A.I., a World
您知道，我们发布了三款芯片。
我们推出了全新的人工智能世界
Foundation model, and first of its kind.
And we announced our work in three areas
基础模型，这是同类中的第一个模型。
我们宣布了我们在机器人技术三个领域
in robotics.
Right.
的工作。
是的。
And they're all important.
And, you know, the the thing, of course,
而且它们都很重要。
当然，您知道，事情
we announced a brand new Blackwell RTX
and has a new AI technology called
我们发布了全新的 Blackwell RTX
并拥有一项名为
neural negotiators.
And we're combining artificial
神经谈判器的新人工智能技术。
我们正在将人工
intelligence and and classical compute.
Let's go to RTX, the new RTX.
智能与经典计算相结合。
让我们转向 RTX，新的 RTX。
Yeah.
We've become so accustomed to your story
是的。
我们已经习惯了您的故事
being dominant in a market for high
performance CPU's server racks data
在高端市场占据主导地位
性能CPU的服务器机架数据
centers.
This is going back to your roots.
中心。
这将回到你的根源。
It's in the desktop context.
There's one right there later in the
它位于桌面上下文中。
稍后在
year laptop.
But for a target base that is developers
年笔记本电脑中就有一个。
但针对的目标群体是开发人员
and nerdy hardcore gamers.
What's the future of that business for
和书呆子硬核游戏玩家。
对于您来说，该业务的未来是什么？
you?
I computer graphics is going to be here
？
我的计算机图形学将永远存在
forever.
Forever.
。
永远。
And
what we've done is we've fused
并且
我们所做的是融合
artificial intelligence and computer
graphics together, and the images that
人工智能和计算机
图形放在一起，
we're generating today wouldn't be
possible if not for the fact that we're
我们今天生成的图像将不会
如果不是因为我们
using computer graphics to create
beautiful pixels and then use artificial
使用计算机图形来创建这一事实，这是可能的
漂亮的像素，然后使用人工
intelligence to amplify that capability.
For example, you know, out of four
智能来增强这种能力。
例如，您知道，在我昨天讨论的四个
frames I was talking about yesterday, 33
million pixels to sell in 4K.
帧中，有 33 个
百万像素以 4K 格式出售。
Now, out of that 33 million pixels, 2
million pixels were computed.
现在，在这 3300 万像素中，有 2
计算了 100 万像素。
The other 31 million pixels were
generated by AI.
另外 3100 万像素是
由AI生成。
In other words, the AI predicts what it
thinks.
换句话说，AI预测它的内容
认为。
The pixels.
That's right.
像素。
没错。
Yeah.
The ultimate generative A.I..
是的。
终极生成式人工智能..
But what was interesting for me is the
focus again was away from the graphics
但对我来说有趣的是
焦点再次远离图形
cards of way from Blackwell to underpin
nets and Cosmos.
从 Blackwell 到支撑的卡片
nets 和 Cosmos。
We probably don't have time to explain
in full detail Cosmos, but you call it a
我们可能没有时间解释
完整详细的 Cosmos，但您将其称为
world Foundation model.
Cosmos is for the physical world.
世界基础模型。
Cosmos 是针对物理世界的。
What Chad shipped is four words and
text.
Chad 发布的是四个字，
That's the easiest way to think about
that.
这是最简单的思考方式
Okay, so this model text input bots can
generate synthetic data in multiple
好的，所以这个模型文本输入机器人可以
在多个
mediums.
It understands the physical world.
介质中生成合成数据。
它理解物理世界。
So, for example, if I ask you the
question, if I ask you to generate
因此，例如，如果我问你
问题，如果我要求你生成
multiple features of a car driving down
the road, it would understand the
汽车行驶的多个特征
在路上，它会了解
dynamics of the world.
It would understand the object
世界的动态。
它会理解对象
permanence and would understand
understand geometry in space, and it
持久性并且会理解
了解空间中的几何形状，
would create a driving scenario for the
car that is plausible.
将为
看起来似乎是这样的汽车。
And so and you open sourced it.
So I don't really think about it as a
所以你开源了它。
所以我并不真正认为它是一个
product or a go to market.
It's more about what Cosmos enables.
产品或进入市场。
更重要的是 Cosmos 能够实现什么。
Is that how we should think about it?
Yeah, Well, the autonomous vehicle
我们应该如何思考它？
是的，嗯，自动驾驶汽车
industry and the robotics industry is
really important to us and we offer
行业和机器人行业是
对我们来说非常重要，我们为他们提供了
three computers for them.
We offer it, of course, the training
三台计算机。
当然，我们通过 TJX 提供培训
computer through through TJX, the
robotics computer that's inside the car
计算机，
车内的机器人计算机
or inside of Roman.
And now we have this new computer called
或罗马内部。
现在我们有了这台新计算机
Omniverse with Cosmos that is the
digital twin or the playground where
Omniverse with Cosmos，它是
数字孪生或游乐场
these robots can learn how to be robots.
And so if we could accelerate the
这些机器人可以学习如何成为机器人。
因此，如果我们能够加速
development of artificial intelligence
for Avs and for robotics, it brings in a
人工智能的发展
对于自动驾驶汽车和机器人技术来说，它为我们带来了很多业务
lot of business for us.
Of course, there's an academic point of
。
当然，这里有一个学术点
tension here.
If I may, Elon Musk is a customer of
紧张。
如果可以的话，埃隆·马斯克是
yours and Tesla.
The theory or practice is based on real
您和特斯拉的客户。
理论或实践基于通过视觉收集的真实
world data gathered through vision.
Yeah.
世界数据。
是的。
Does the synthetic data underpinning of
Cosmos kind of contradict that?
合成数据是否支持
Cosmos 有点矛盾？
It doesn't replace.
It augments.
它不会取代。
它增强了。
And so you're going to you should
collect as much world data as you can.
所以你应该
尽可能多地收集世界数据。
Of course, collecting world data is very
expensive and Elon has a great advantage
当然，收集世界数据非常重要
昂贵，埃隆有很大的优势
because, number one, he has his own
factory for his cars, is fantastic, has
因为，第一，他有自己的
他的汽车工厂非常棒，里面有很多视频设备。
a lot of video gear in it.
His AVI algorithms is incredible.
他的 AVI 算法令人难以置信。
It's the best in the world and and he
has a very large fleet of cars on the
这是世界上最好的，而且他
road that allows him to collect a lot of
data.
道路上有一支非常庞大的车队，这使他能够收集大量
And so so I think he has just a
phenomenal position and he's been
所以我认为他只有一个
非凡的地位，他已经为此工作了很长时间
working on this for a long time.
And so he's he's going to be in a great
。
因此，他将处于一个很好的
position to to take advantage of it.
Well, may I ask you, at this juncture,
位置来利用它。
好吧，我可以问你，在这个节骨眼上，
he's clearly influential in this
upcoming administration, but he also
他显然在这件事上有影响力
即将到来的政府，但他也
positions Tesla as a leading air and
robotics company.
将特斯拉定位为领先的空气和
机器人公司。
Yeah, very.
How does that vote for him?
是的，非常。
这对他的投票结果如何？
Video Elon Musk's influence on President
elect Trump and.
视频埃隆·马斯克对总统的影响
选举特朗普和。
And also the incoming administration's
kind of attitude towards I,
还有即将上任的政府
对我的态度，
I don't know, the the the the attitude
towards it.
我不知道，这个态度
I, I know Elon's attitude towards the
and and he's very optimistic about the
我，我知道埃隆对
他对未来非常乐观
future.
And obviously he's working on some of
。
显然他正在研究一些
the most important areas.
He's working on foundation cognitive
最重要的领域。
他正在研究基础认知
intelligence i i.
His.
智能。
他的。
Tesla is working on Thomas vehicles and
optimizes for him nor robotics.
特斯拉正在研发 Thomas 车辆和
既不适合他，也不适合机器人。
These three areas of A.I.
are the three most important areas of
人工智能的这三个领域。
是人工智能最重要的三个领域
A.I..
And so I think I think he's working on
人工智能..
所以我认为他正在做
exactly the right things.
You kind of positioned and video is
完全正确的事情。
您的定位和视频
positioned in the supply chain for
physical A.I.
在供应链中的定位
物理人工智能
robotics, autonomous driving.
Explain that a bit more, the role you
机器人、自动驾驶。
再解释一下，您在视频播放中看到的角色
see in video play.
Well, we're a core technology company,
。
嗯，我们是一家核心技术公司，
and so we build the foundational
computing platforms.
因此我们构建了基础技术
计算平台。
We're also full stack.
And so we developed the necessary
我们也是全栈。
因此我们开发了必要的
algorithms and necessary A.I.
technologies, and then we put it and we
算法和必要的人工智能。
技术，然后我们将其发布
put it out to the industry for them to
adopt it and turn it into end market
将其发布给业界，让他们
采用它并将其转化为终端市场
solutions where we're computing platform
companies.
我们作为计算平台的解决方案
公司。
So you're on stage and you're surrounded
by, I think, a dozen humanoid robots,
所以你在舞台上，你在包围
我认为是由十几个人形机器人组成的，
which is nice for you.
When will I be here at CES in Las Vegas
这对你来说很好。
我什么时候会在拉斯维加斯参加 CES
and actually have there some robots
right now in real terms?
并且实际上有一些机器人
现在就实际而言？
You must have a timeline that you see
real world commercial deployment of the
您必须有一个看到的时间表
您昨晚概述的技术的实际商业部署
technology you outlined last night.
It depends on on use case.
。
这取决于用例。
I would say first use the first use case
will probably be in manufacturing.
我会说首先使用第一个用例
可能会投入生产。
You know, there's
estimates tens if not 100 million jobs
你知道，有
估计有数十个甚至一亿个工作岗位
that are workers that are the world is
short of workers and
这些都是世界上的工人
劳动力短缺和
aging population declining declining
birth rates.
人口老龄化下降
出生率。
And and so I think the the world needs a
lot more workers.
所以我认为世界需要一个
更多的工人。
Robotics is one of the best ways for us
to supplement all of that and help
机器人是我们最好的方法之一
补充所有这些并帮助
companies recover the lost revenues on
the one hand and drive productivity,
公司收回损失的收入
一方面提高生产力，
which reduces inflation for the world.
On the other hand.
这可以降低世界的通货膨胀。
另一方面。
And so I think robotics is going to be
very important to that in different
所以我认为机器人技术将会
这对于不同的
different areas.
So you could have probably deploy to
不同领域非常重要。
因此，您可能首先部署到
manufacturing first because they
obviously need it most, which you see is
制造，因为它们
显然最需要它，您看到的是
a ginormous potential market
addressable.
一个巨大的潜在市场
可寻址。
It's a $50 trillion industry that wants
to grow and things to grow.
这是一个价值 50 万亿美元的行业，需要
成长，万物成长。
Sorry to interrupt you.
Jensen.
很抱歉打扰您。
Jensen。
It's interesting that Wall Street is
struggling with this morning, among many
有趣的是，华尔街
今天早上在许多事情中苦苦挣扎
things, is
they understand investment there that
事情之一是
他们了解那里的投资
drains the foundation models.
In terms of Nvidia's business model,
会耗尽基础模型的资源。
就 Nvidia 的商业模式而言，
what you outlined last night, Cosmos and
then later on, on the inference side,
您昨晚概述的 Cosmos 和
然后，在推理方面，
how physical AI helps grow your business
from that drives growth.
物理 AI 如何帮助您发展业务
由此推动增长。
Just simple as that.
Yeah, as simple as that.
就这么简单。
是的，就这么简单。
I think if you if you just look at
simply like we have three computers and
我想如果你看看
就像我们有三台计算机和
two of the computers and omniverse
drives an enormous amount of data that
两台计算机和全宇宙
驱动大量数据
is necessary to train the A.I.
models.
这是训练人工智能所必需的。
模型。
Right?
And so Omniverse creates the data that
对吗？
因此 Omniverse 创建了数据
we then use to train A.I.
models.
我们然后用它来训练人工智能。
模型。
The training is what drives direct
sales.
培训是直接驱动力
销售。
And the more robots that are that are
available, the more data we can create,
机器人越多
可用的数据越多，我们可以创建的数据越多，
the more A.I.
models we have to.
人工智能就越多。
我们必须去的模型。
We have to go train.
That's that cycle is ultimately what
我们必须去火车。
这就是我们最终追求的循环
we're striving for.
All of that drives consumption from data
。
所有这些都推动了数据消耗
center growth.
There is a surge in AI spending, data
中心的增长。
人工智能支出激增，数据
center growth.
Mm hmm.
中心增长。
嗯嗯。
Some of our audience are a bit concerned
about how sustainable that is.
我们的一些观众有点担心
关于其可持续性如何。
Short, medium and long term.
Well, at the at the limit, artificial
短期、中期和长期。
嗯，在极限情况下，人工
intelligence is the single most
important technology force of our time.
智能是最重要的
我们这个时代的重要技术力量。
And and it's really about we're at the
beginning of that.
而且这确实是我们正处于
And in the future, every single data
center will be
在未来，每一个数据
中心将由人工智能驱动
driven by AI and and the type of
computing that we build today.
我们今天构建的计算。
And and so if you look at the world
today, we're about a year and a half
如果你看看这个世界
今天，我们已经进行了大约一年半
into the remodeling, if you will, the
modernization and the reinvention of
改造，如果你愿意的话，
现代化和计算的重塑。
computing.
And so I think that over the next
计算。
所以我认为在接下来的几年里，您将会看到
从旧的计算方式过渡
several years, you're going to see the
transition from the old way of doing
computing, general purpose computing.
This is a new way of doing computing,
计算，通用计算。
这是一种新的计算方式，
artificial intelligence and accelerated
computing.
人工智能和加速
计算。
And so we have a lot of growth to go to.
Let's go back to your and Nvidia's
因此我们还有很大的增长空间。
让我们回到你和 Nvidia 的
roots, and therein lies the complication
behind the story Accelerated computing.
根源，这就是复杂性所在
故事背后加速计算。
You spent four years redefining the
computer for me, but then we get RTX
您花了四年时间重新定义了
我的电脑，但随后我们得到了 RTX
Blackwell single.
BLACKWELL In that form factor, the
Blackwell single。
BLACKWELL 在这种外形尺寸中，
target audience is hardcore gamers, but
also developers.
目标受众是铁杆游戏玩家，但是
还有开发人员。
And I wondered if you could give me any
early examples or evidence of how you
我想知道你是否能给我任何
早期示例或证据，说明您如何
see the gaming industry adopting your
technology.
看到游戏行业采用您的
Well, A.I.
is going to re reinvigorate the video
好吧，A.I.
将重振视频
game industry.
On the one hand, for developers, it's
游戏产业。
一方面，对于开发者来说，
going to reduce the cost of creating the
content.
将降低创建
内容。
On the other hand, all of the characters
that are in the games are going to be
另一方面，所有字符
游戏中的未来将成为
smart characters in the future.
So every time you interact with them,
聪明的角色。
因此，每次您与他们互动时，
they're going to be interacting with you
in a much more intelligent way.
他们也会与您互动
以更加智能的方式。
And so the games are going to be more
interesting, the characters are going to
因此游戏将会更加智能
有趣，角色将会
be more interesting, the content
development costs is going to decline,
更有趣，内容
开发成本将会下降，
and that's going to be really great for
the industry.
这对于
And so I think the future is really
bright for for video games and in these
所以我认为未来真的是
非常适合视频游戏和这些
virtual worlds.
And artificial intelligence is going to
虚拟世界。
人工智能将会真正实现
really.
Project.
。
项目。
Digits.
May I pick it up?
数字。
我可以取一下吗？
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
$3,000.
是啊，是啊，是啊。
3,000 美元。
Yeah.
Digits?
是的。
数字？
Yeah.
A supercomputer.
是的。
一台超级计算机。
Yeah, exactly.
How do you imagine you're just sitting
是的，没错。
您如何想象您只是坐在那里
there just like that?
You're working on your PC?
就这样？
您正在电脑上工作吗？
Well,
why would I need one of these?
嗯，
为什么我需要其中之一？
Probably not me.
But how big is the addressable market
可能不是我。
但这的潜在市场有多大
for for this?
What is the addressable market?
呢？
潜在市场是什么？
There's 30 million software developers
there.
有 3000 万软件开发人员
那里。
Probably something along the lines of 10
million designers around the world.
可能类似于 10
全球 10 万名设计师。
Probably another 20 million creative
artists.
可能还有 2000 万创意人员
艺术家。
Hard to say exactly how many students
I'm going to guess.
很难说到底有多少学生
我猜一下。
Probably a couple of hundred million
students around the world.
可能有几亿
世界各地的学生。
Everybody is going to have to at it.
Everybody's going to have to to what
每个人都必须这样做。
每个人都必须购买他们能买得起的计算机
they can afford computers.
And so here's if they can afford
。
因此，如果他们买得起
computers and they would like to have a
companion that helps them, do I?
计算机并且他们希望拥有一台
帮助他们的伴侣，是吗？
This is the way to do it.
Can I just clarify something?
这就是做到这一点的方法。
我可以澄清一下吗？
I think you said on stage Mac OS Linux
and Windows, But no, no education, said
我想你在台上说的是 Mac OS Linux
和 Windows，但不，没有教育，说
Jocelyn.
No, no.
Jocelyn。
不，不。
Whatever computer you use, you're
literally enjoying how it's going to be
无论您使用什么计算机，您都可以
真正享受它的使用方式
used.
It's sitting right there and you're just
。
它就在那里，您只需
connect to it wirelessly like it's your
personal cloud.
无线连接到它，就像它是您的一样
个人云。
I promised the audience I'd clarify
that.
我向观众保证我会澄清
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're running short on time.
是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊。
我们的时间不多了。
President elect Trump has been speaking
during the course of my conversation.
当选总统特朗普一直在讲话
在我谈话的过程中。
How imperative is it that you go
tomorrow?
你去是多么必要
明天？
I'll go and meet with him.
If Nvidia is America's leading air
我去见他。
如果英伟达是美国领先的航空
company.
And will you?
公司。
你愿意吗？
I'd be delighted to go see him.
Have you been invited?
我很高兴去见他。
您被邀请了吗？
Not yet, but I would be delighted to go
see him and
还没有，但我很乐意去
见到他并
and congratulate him and and do
everything we can to help this
祝贺他并且做
我们将竭尽全力帮助这次管理
administration succeed.
A lot of what you outlined on stage last
取得成功。
您上次在舞台上概述的很多内容
night in the realm of fiscal I you know,
I saw xpeng, for example, in the
晚上在财政领域，我知道，
例如，我在
autonomous driving context that's
happening in China, Like they are doing
自动驾驶环境
发生在中国，就像他们在机器人技术方面做了很多工作
a lot on robotics.
So I'm going to ask you about tariffs.
。
所以我要问你有关关税的问题。
You know, it's likely this coming
administration will be as restrictive on
你知道，很可能会这样
政府将对
technology exports and tariffs will be a
function.
技术出口和关税实施同样的限制
How have you prepared for that?
Jensen?
您为此做了哪些准备？
Jensen？
Well, whatever whatever the
administration ultimately decides, we'll
好吧，不管怎样
管理部门最终决定，我们将
give them as much insight as we can from
our perspective.
为他们提供尽可能多的见解
我们的观点。
And I'm sure that the administration
will make the right moves that's in the
我确信政府
将做出符合我们国家最大利益的正确举措。
best interest of our country.
2025.
2025 年。
I kind of started the conversation by
saying a lot has changed since we last
我是这样开始对话的
自从我们上次在夏天讲话以来发生了很多变化
spoke in the summer.
You said that the age of general
。
您说通用机器人时代即将到来。
robotics is just around the corner.
Is 2025 the year of general robotics, or
机器人时代即将到来。
2025 年是通用机器人年，还是
is that a little premature to your mind?
The development is going going
您认为这有点为时过早？
开发正在进行
gangbusters, as you can see, all the
different robots that are going to be
如您所见，所有
不同的机器人将在这里
around here and the enabling technology
necessary for general robotics is coming
以及支持技术
通用机器人技术所必需的技术即将到来
together.
All the pieces are coming together.
一起。
所有的部分都整合在一起。
The industry still has a lot of
engineering to do.
该行业仍然有很多
工程要做。
If you if you look long term, you know,
pick your horizon in ten or 20 years,
如果你着眼长远，你知道，
选择十年或二十年后的视野，
the number of robots that's going to be
on Earth is going to be measured in
机器人的数量
地球上的测量单位为
probably tens, if not hundreds and
potentially billions of robots.
可能是数十，如果不是数百，
可能有数十亿个机器人。
And so those those days are clearly
coming.
所以那些日子显然是
即将到来。
Is it going to happen in the next couple
of years or the next five years?
接下来的几个时间里会发生这种情况吗
几年还是未来五年？
Hard to say, But the development of
robotics is going to be all over the
很难说，但是发展
机器人技术现在将遍布全世界
world now.
And we're seeing startup companies,
。
我们看到初创公司、
large companies, industrial companies,
consumer electronics companies all
大型公司、工业公司、
消费电子公司都
getting involved in the future of
robotics.
参与到未来
机器人技术。
And our offering to the industry is a
three computer system.
我们为行业提供的是
三个计算机系统。
And so whether they're developing the
robot training, the robot, we have
所以他们是否正在开发
机器人训练，机器人，我们有用于它们的系统和 GE X 云
systems for them and GE X clouds for
them.
他们。
If they're simulating the robots, we
have omniverse for them.
如果他们正在模拟机器人，我们
为他们提供全能宇宙。
And if they want to deploy that when
they're ready to deploy the robots, we
如果他们想在
他们已经准备好部署机器人了，我们
have, you know, little or little,
little, little computers that basically
你知道，有一点点，
很小很小的计算机，基本上
is the computer brain of the robot that
they can put inside a robot.
是机器人的计算机大脑
他们可以放入机器人内。
And so we'll work with the industry
across the board from the development of
因此我们将与业界合作
一刀切的发展
the world blind to the deployment of the
robot.
全球盲目部署
机器人。
And we have computer systems for them,
algorithms for them, for them, and we'll
我们为它们配备了计算机系统，
为他们服务的算法，为他们服务，我们将
partner with the industry to make this
future happen very, very quick.
与业界合作来实现这一目标
未来发生得非常非常快。
Which line of business grows fastest
this year?
哪条业务增长最快
今年？
Datacenter, gaming or other, they're all
going to grow fast.
数据中心、游戏或其他，它们都是
将会快速增长。
I think gaming is continuing to grow.
Our our autonomous vehicle business is
我认为游戏正在持续增长。
我们的自动驾驶汽车业务
already on its way to be a $5 billion
business just this year.
已迈向 50 亿美元的目标
今年刚开始营业。
And so right and right run rate.
And so the autonomous vehicle business
所以运行速度非常正确。
因此，自动驾驶汽车业务刚刚开始起步
is is just starting to get off the
ground.
地面。
And that tells you something about how
we address it.
这告诉你一些关于如何
我们解决了这个问题。
And the reason for that is we get the
benefit from the beginning of the
原因是我们得到了
受益于AIS的发展
development of the AIS all the way to
the deployment of the cars, because a
汽车的调配，因为
car company needs to factories, a car
factory that builds the cars and an AI
汽车公司需要工厂、一辆汽车
制造汽车的工厂和人工智能
factory that builds the AIS for the
cars.
为汽车制造 AIS 的工厂
汽车。
And both of these the both of these
areas, we get to participate.
这两个都是
地区，我们可以参与。
And so I think it's going to be a very
large business.
所以我认为这将是一个非常
大型企业。
Jensen I've made you late for your next
appointment.
Jensen 我让你迟到了
约会。
Yeah, it's great to see you.
Really grateful for your time.
是的，很高兴见到你。
非常感谢您抽出宝贵时间。
It's good to see you.
While Jensen won the immediacy.
很高兴见到您。
而 Jensen 赢得了即时性。